<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>EOS Learning Resources on EOS Learning Resources by EOS Costa Rica</title>
    <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in EOS Learning Resources on EOS Learning Resources by EOS Costa Rica</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2016 21:07:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://learn.eoscostarica.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The EOS Blockchain</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/eos-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/eos-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>Introduction The EOS.IO software introduces a new blockchain architecture designed to enable vertical and horizontal scaling of decentralized applications. This is achieved by creating an operating system-like construct upon which applications can be built. The software provides accounts, authentication, databases, asynchronous communication and the scheduling of applications across many CPU cores or clusters. The resulting technology is a blockchain architecture that may ultimately scale to millions of transactions per second, eliminates user fees, and allows for quick and easy deployment and maintenance of decentralized applications, in the context of a governed blockchain</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Content</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/adding-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/adding-content/</guid>
      <description>Hello world Let&amp;rsquo;s create our first content file for your documentation. Open a terminal and add the following command for each new file you want to add. Replace &amp;lt;section-name&amp;gt; with a general term that describes your document in detail.
hugo new &amp;lt;section-name&amp;gt;/filename.md  Visitors of your website will find the final document under www.example.com/&amp;lt;section-name&amp;gt;/filename/.
Since it&amp;rsquo;s possible to have multiple content files in the same section I recommend to create at least one index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Delegated Proof of Stake</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/delegated-proof-of-stake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/delegated-proof-of-stake/</guid>
      <description>What is a consensus algorithm ? A consensus algorithm is a process in computer science used to achieve agreement on a single data value among distributed processes or systems.
Blockchain technology relies on consensus algorithms to reach agreement among nodes. A blockchain can be thought of as a decentralized database that is managed by distributed computers on a peer-to-peer (P2P) network. Each peer maintains a copy of the ledger to prevent a single point of failure (SPOF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Block Producer</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/block-producer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:08:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/block-producer/</guid>
      <description>What is a Block Producer? Block producers provide the infrastructure required to run the underlying network layer to process all transactions. Some block producers run their own &amp;ldquo;Bare Metal Servers&amp;rdquo; meaning they own and operate their own physical equipment . Other Block producers provide the service by using third party cloud services.
The &amp;ldquo;Delegated Proof of Stake&amp;rdquo; or DPoS consensus algorithm, which is the system that EOS.IO operates on, Block Producers replace the concept of “miners” as the custodians of the network, Technical White Paper.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOS Costa Rica Dev Learning Tools</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 09:24:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/tools/</guid>
      <description>EOS Costa Rica Tools Our development team is constantly working on providing new tools to help the community build on EOS and learn from our experiences, here is a lost of tools we have made available to the community so far.
EOS dApp Development Environment A docker compose based development environment for EOS dApp Development. This is easiest way maintain a local environment for development that is guaranteed to work out-of-the-box across the different host operating systems: Mac OS, Windows and Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Contributing Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/open-source/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/open-source/</guid>
      <description>Development Process We use a Kanban-style board to prioritize the work. For example the dmeetup project board.
We have added a additional column to the default automated board in order to maintain a prioritized To Do column. When a new issues is create you need to explicitly use the project option on the Github issue to include it in the board; Once you do that it gets automatically added to the New Issues column.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOS Smart Contracts</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/smart-contracts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 14:51:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/smart-contracts/</guid>
      <description>EOS Smart Contracts How to develop your first EOS dAPP Step by Step – Part 1 : EOSIO Setup
How to develop your first EOS dAPP Step by Step – Part 2 : Smart Contract
How to develop your first EOS dAPP Step by Step – Part 3 : Web dApp</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOS Costa Rica Presentations</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 20:20:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/presentations/</guid>
      <description> Slide Decks PowerPoint formatted presentations from previous community meet-ups.
 Intro to Blockchain
 Blockchain 3.0
  EOS Costa Rica Design Assets  Logos  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eos Funds</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/eos-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 20:20:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/eos-funds/</guid>
      <description>WIP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Governance</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/governance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 14:52:06 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/governance/</guid>
      <description>Ricardian Contracts WIP</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resource Usage</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/resource-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 14:51:37 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/resource-usage/</guid>
      <description> There are three broad classes of resources that are consumed by applications:

Bandwidth and Log Storage (Disk); Computation and Computational Backlog (CPU) State Storage (RAM) RAM market </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOS accounts</title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/eos-accounts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 14:50:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/eos-accounts/</guid>
      <description>Creating wallet and importing keys 
Creating an EOS account 
How to generate an EOS key pair safely OFFLINE</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://learn.eoscostarica.io/reading-list/</guid>
      <description>EOS Costa Rica Recommended Reading List Review and Buy on Amazon
 Irrational Exuberance: Revised and Expanded Third Edition by Robert J. Shiller (Paperback)
 Bad Blood: Secrets and Lies in a Silicon Valley Startup by John Carreyrou (Hardcover)
 Fooled by Randomness: The Hidden Role of Chance in Life and in the Markets (Incerto) by Nassim Nicholas Taleb (Paperback)
 The Money Game by Adam Smith (Paperback)
 The Origin of Wealth: The Radical Remaking of Economics and What it Means for Business and Society by Eric D.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>